{
    "id": "fab79b09e4624fb397d72392f30671b4",
    "title": "General Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Do you enjoy ………………. models from clay?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to make",
                "make",
                "to making",
                "making"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "While holidaying in Sydney, Martin  …………….. a strong Australian accent.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "caught",
                "acquired",
                "earned",
                "gained"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "...................... he was, he played well.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Though tired",
                "Tired though",
                "As tired",
                "Although tired"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "………………. she was, she could not react at all.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Though shocked",
                "Although shocked",
                "Shocked as",
                "As shocked"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The front door was open, ……………… nobody was at home.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "but",
                "and",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The bell has already .......................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "rang",
                "ring",
                "rung",
                "ringing"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Stella ………………….. wait for her birthday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can hardly",
                "can't hardly",
                "won't hardly",
                "couldn't hardly"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "There were ………………… students in the class than expected.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "few",
                "fewer",
                "less",
                "lesser"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I did ..................... work today than yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "less",
                "lesser",
                "few",
                "fewer"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Dad has …………………. on the sofa all morning.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "lay",
                "laid",
                "lain"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}